// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "REM sleep occupies...... % of total sleep time in all ages",
    answer: "D. 20 - 25%",
    options: [
      "A. 20-50%",
      "B. 25 - 45%",
      "C. 30 - 45%",
      "D. 20 - 25%",
      "E. 45 - 55%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is true?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Cholinergic neurons are active during sleep",
      "cholinergic neurons are inactive during slow wave sleep",
      "Cholinergic neurons are inactive during NON-REM sleep",
      "Cholinergic neurons are active in both waking and sleeping periods",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following scientists were the first to investigate the neuronal component regulating the brain sleep - wake mechanism?",
    answer: "C and D only",
    options: [
      "Hans Berger",
      "Alfred Loomis",
      "Moruzzi",
      "Magoun",
      "C and D only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The RAS is involved in which of the following?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "activation of the cortex",
      "maintaining muscle tone of antigravity muscle",
      "assisting in regulation of heart beat",
      "All of the above",
      " A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following produced the FIRO(Fundamental Interpersonal Relations Orientation) theory to examine group dynamics?",
    answer: "William Schutz",
    options: [
      "Wilfred Bion",
      "William Schutz",
      "Bruce Tuckman",
      "Irvin Yalom",
      "Hollingshead and Redlich"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not true about sociology?",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "It is a scientific discipline",
      "It has many approaches and paradigms",
      "Concepts are the building blocks",
      "Looks at society using concepts",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The Four main methods of sociological research includes the following except ",
    answer: "outreaches",
    options: [
      "Experiments",
      "Surveys",
      "Field methods",
      "outreaches",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Sociology relies on which of the following paradigms to investigate society?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Theory",
      "Data",
      "Analysis",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Sociology as a quest to understand patterns of behaviour is found in which of the following disciplines",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Psychology",
      "Political science",
      "Psychiatry",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "According to Hess, Markson and Stein, sociology is which of the following?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "the systematic study of human behaviour",
      "the groups to which one belongs",
      "the societies that human beings create and within which their lives unfold",
      "All of the above",
      "A and C only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following is true in anxiety disorders?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "poor executive functioning",
      "Poor neuropsychological performance in attention",
      "poor performance in memory",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What percentage of depressed patients have cognitive impairment?",
    answer: "50 - 70%",
    options: [
      "50 - 80%",
      "60 - 90%",
      "45 - 75%",
      "50 - 70%",
      "65 - 85%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Experts are more likely to use which problem solving technique that are not available to the novice",
    answer: "Heuristic",
    options: [
      "Trial and error",
      "Algorithm",
      "Heuristic",
      "Insight",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Problem-solving strategies include the following except ",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Trial and errors",
      "Insight",
      "Algorithm",
      "Heuristic technique",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The process of reasoning from one or more general statements to reach a logically certain conclusion is",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Deductive reasoning",
      "Deductive logic",
      "Logical deduction",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "In thinking, we make use of the following?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "concepts",
      "prototypes",
      "cores",
      "All of the above",
      "B and C only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which of the following is true about thinking?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "said to occur in all parts of the brain",
      "the prefrontal cortex modulates rational thinking and is involved with decision making ",
      "thinking helps us define and organize experiences",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which of the following is true about the hippocampus?",
    answer: "critical in declarative memory",
    options: [
      "critical in declarative memory",
      "Necessary for procedural memory",
      "essential for memory storage",
      "damage affects procedural memory",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The hearing functions of the temporal lobe in the non-dominant hemisphere include",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "naming of musical scores",
      "verbal aspect of memory ",
      "all the semantic aspect music",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Basic sensory function of the temporal lobe include the following",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "processing auditory input",
      "Visual object recognition",
      "Long term storage of sensory input",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Which of the following connections of the temporal lobes is correctly matched with its function",
    answer: "Medial temporal pathway - -long term memory ",
    options: [
      "Hierarchical sensory pathway - - directing movements with respect to auditory information",
      "Dorsal auditory pathway - - stimulus Categorisation",
      "Polymodal pathway - - necessary for various aspects of movement control, affect and short-term memory",
      "Medial temporal pathway - -long term memory ",
      "Frontal Lobe projection - - stimulus recognition"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Paul D. Maclean expanded the Papez Circuit to include the following",
    answer: "A and B only",
    options: [
      "Prefrontal cortex",
      "Amygdala",
      "Dentate cortex",
      "Posterior Thalamic nucleus",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Lesions in the amygdala can  lead to the following except ",
    answer: "Hyperorality",
    options: [
      "agitation",
      "Irritability",
      "Hyperorality",
      "paranoia",
      "psychosis"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 24,
    question: "Which of the following is true about the Primary auditory cortex?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Brodmann areas 41 and 42",
      "transverse gyri",
      "Heschl's gyri",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "The medial temporal region (Limbic Cortex) includes ",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Entorhinal cortex",
      "Subiculum",
      "Perirhinal cortex",
      "All of the above",
      "A and C only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Concerning the temporal lobes, which of the following is true?",
    answer: "approx 17% of the volume of cerebral cortex",
    options: [
      "lateral to the occipital lobes",
      "anterior to the frontal and parietal lobes",
      "Inferior to the Lateral sulcus",
      "approx 17% of the volume of cerebral cortex",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Components of uncinate fits include",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "olfactory aura",
      "involuntary movements",
      "sensations of deja vu and jamais vu",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 28,
    question: "KluverBucy syndrome comprises?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Visual agnosia",
      "Hyperorality",
      "Hypersexuality",
      "All of the above",
      "A and C only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 29,
    question: "The theory of the triune brain was developed by",
    answer: "Paul D. Maclean",
    options: [
      "Scoville and Milner",
      "Paul Kluver and Heinrich Bucy",
      "James Papez",
      "Paul Broca",
      "Paul D. Maclean"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 30,
    question: "A gene or sequence of DNA that occurs in two or more common forms is",
    answer: "polymorphism",
    options: [
      "Restriction Fragment Length Polymorphism",
      "recombinant DNA",
      "polymorphism",
      "Alleles",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Techniques in molecular genetics include the following ",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "molecular cloning",
      "Gene tracking",
      "Direct gene analysis",
      "Linkage studies",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 32,
    question: "Higher-level organization of nucleic acids in chromatin and histones refers to which structure of the human genome",
    answer: "Quaternary",
    options: [
      "Primary",
      "Secondary",
      "Tertiary",
      "Quaternary",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 33,
    question: "Which of the following refers to the coding regions in the human genome ",
    answer: "Exons",
    options: [
      "introns",
      "Exons",
      "histones",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 34,
    question: "Which of the following is true about mitochondrial inheritance?",
    answer: "Law of segregation",
    options: [
      "Law of independent assortment",
      "Law of dominance",
      "Law of segregation",
      "Law of inheritability",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 35,
    question: "Mendel's first law is also known as",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Psychology",
      "Political science",
      "Psychiatry",
      "All of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 36,
    question: "Which of the following published the theory of use and disuse?",
    answer: "Jean Lamarck",
    options: [
      "Charles Darwin",
      "Gregor Mendel",
      "Jean Lamarck",
      "Thomas Rutherford ",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Examples of perceptual disturbance include the following except ",
    answer: "None of the above",
    options: [
      "Capgras syndrome",
      "Fregoli",
      "Intermetamorphosis",
      "Delusion of subjective doubles",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 38,
    question: "The following is true about the trichromatic theory",
    answer: "Combination of the three colours create other colours",
    options: [
      "it is based in the work of Thomas Young alone",
      "The retina has three types of colour receptor cones: Blue, Green and yellow",
      "Colour blindness have normal Green sensory cones",
      "Combination of the three colours create other colours",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 39,
    question: "The Four possible stimulus/response situations include",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Hit",
      "Miss",
      "False alarm",
      "Correct rejection",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Which of the following is true according to Weber's law",
    answer: "The smaller the stimulus, the smaller the change required to notice anything different",
    options: [
      "The larger a stimulus, the smaller the change required to notice anything different",
      "The weaker a stimulus, the larger the change required to notice anything different",
      "The smaller the stimulus, the larger the change required to notice any difference",
      "The smaller the stimulus, the smaller the change required to notice anything different",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 41,
    question: "Diminished sensitivity as a result of constant stimulation is",
    answer: "Adaptation",
    options: [
      "Transduction",
      "Adaptation",
      "Activation",
      "Acclimatization",
      "Sensation"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 42,
    question: "The conversion of stimulus energy into neural impulses by the sensory receptors is referred to as",
    answer: "Transduction",
    options: [
      "Adaptation",
      "Sensation",
      "Transduction",
      "Transmission",
      "C and D only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 43,
    question: "Which of the following is the basic building blocks of perception",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Transduction",
      "Sensation",
      "Stimuli",
      "Adaptation",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 44,
    question: "Contributions of Anthropology to Psychiatry includes the following",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "emphasizing the relevance of social environment in the diagnosis, treatment and prognosis of Psychiatric ailments",
      "creating concepts and methods that psychiatrists are able to apply",
      "the development of socially optimal Psychiatric programmes",
      "secures the development of politics and programmes implying close interconnectedness of social conditions and mental health",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 45,
    question: "The reification of a nosological category developed for a particular cultural group that is then applied to members of another culture for whom it lacks coherence and its validity has not been established",
    answer: "Categorical fallacy",
    options: [
      "Categorical fallacy",
      "Transcultural fallacy",
      "Anthropological Categorisation",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 46,
    question: "Basic sensory function of the temporal lobe include the following",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "processing auditory input",
      "Visual object recognition",
      "Long term storage of sensory input",
      "All of the above",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Which of the following connections of the temporal lobes is correctly matched with its function",
    answer: "Medial temporal pathway - -long term memory ",
    options: [
      "Hierarchical sensory pathway - - directing movements with respect to auditory information",
      "Dorsal auditory pathway - - stimulus Categorisation",
      "Polymodal pathway - - necessary for various aspects of movement control, affect and short-term memory",
      "Medial temporal pathway - -long term memory ",
      "Frontal Lobe projection - - stimulus recognition"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Paul D. Maclean expanded the Papez Circuit to include the following",
    answer: "A and B only",
    options: [
      "Prefrontal cortex",
      "Amygdala",
      "Dentate cortex",
      "Posterior Thalamic nucleus",
      "A and B only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Lesions in the amygdala can  lead to the following except ",
    answer: "Hyperorality",
    options: [
      "agitation",
      "Irritability",
      "Hyperorality",
      "paranoia",
      "psychosis"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 50,
    question: "The Four Anthropological Questions for Psychiatry includes",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "To what extent do Psychiatric disorders differ in different societies?",
      "What place does translation have in cross-cultural research?",
      "Does the standard approach to cross-cultural research in psychiatry commit a 'category fallacy'?",
      "All of the above",
      "A and C only"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "The medial temporal region (Limbic Cortex) includes ",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Entorhinal cortex",
      "Subiculum",
      "Perirhinal cortex",
      "All of the above",
      "A and C only"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Concerning the temporal lobes, which of the following is true?",
    answer: "approx 17% of the volume of cerebral cortex",
    options: [
      "lateral to the occipital lobes",
      "anterior to the frontal and parietal lobes",
      "Inferior to the Lateral sulcus",
      "approx 17% of the volume of cerebral cortex",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },



  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];